<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>origoss on Universal</title><link>/web-universal/tags/origoss/</link><description>Recent content in origoss on Universal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/web-universal/tags/origoss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WFH</title><link>/web-universal/blog/2020/05/02/wfh/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>/web-universal/blog/2020/05/02/wfh/</guid><description>Hatodik hete dolgozunk otthonról. Most már mondhatjuk hogy belejöttünk. Közben két új kollégával bővült a csapatunk és az ő beilleszkedésük is gördülékenyen zajlott. Mi ezzel a hozzáállással és a speciális szaktudásunkban bízva alkalmazkodunk az új körülményekhez.</description></item><item><title>Shape the cloud, not the client</title><link>/web-universal/blog/2020/03/02/diary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>/web-universal/blog/2020/03/02/diary/</guid><description>A series of articles about our own experiences in the field of cloud native consulting. The first is about how to be independent of cloud service providers. #kubernetes #k8s #cloudnative #cncf #cloudnativediaries</description></item><item><title>Kubecon sponsor</title><link>/web-universal/blog/2019/09/02/sponsor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>/web-universal/blog/2019/09/02/sponsor/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Origoss joined CNCF</title><link>/web-universal/blog/2019/08/02/join/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>/web-universal/blog/2019/08/02/join/</guid><description>I am proud to announce that Origoss Solutions has joined the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF).
CNCF is an open source software foundation dedicated to making cloud native computing universal and sustainable. Cloud native computing uses an open source software stack to deploy applications as microservices, packaging each part into its own container, and dynamically orchestrating those containers to optimize resource utilization. Cloud native technologies enable software developers to build and deploy great products faster.</description></item><item><title>Red Hat Advanced Solution Provider</title><link>/web-universal/blog/2019/07/02/announce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>/web-universal/blog/2019/07/02/announce/</guid><description>I am proud to announce that Origoss Solutions is now a Red Hat Advanced Solution Provider with a Cloud Infrastructure / PaaS specialization.
Red Hat OpenShift is a comprehensive enterprise-grade application platform, built for containers with Kubernetes.
As a Red Hat Advanced Solution Provider and as a Kubernetes Certified Service Provider, we help our customers in their successful Cloud Native transformation, leveraging our several decades of experience in consulting, developing, supporting legacy network and IT system operation.</description></item></channel></rss>